<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Container Field Types on Documentation</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/</link><description>Recent content in Container Field Types on Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accordion</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/accordion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/accordion/</guid><description>Accordion # The accordion field is a container field. It can define multiple input fields, which are displayed as subform. The output is an array of dictionaries.
Accordion
Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique title string mandatory The title of the accordion element dynFormSearchKey string optional (default: null) key of one of the child field of which the value refers to a custom partial form dynFormObjectFile string with relative path to file without file extension optional (default: null) if dynFormSearchKey is set this path points to the file containing a subform.</description></item><item><title>Bundle manager</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/bundle-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/bundle-manager/</guid><description>Bundle manager # The bundle-manager is a container field for creating a file-manager form for managing the assets of page bundles. The word page bundle refers to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s Page Bundles. A page bundle is a way of organizing a page inside it&amp;rsquo;s own directory together with it&amp;rsquo;s resources.
It&amp;rsquo;s not possible to use Bundle managers with pages which are not stored as page bundle.
Bundle Manager together with a Bundle Image Thumbnail</description></item><item><title>Leaf array</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/leaf-array/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/leaf-array/</guid><description>Leaf array # The lead array field is a container field for a single child field. The output is a collection of values of the child field value type.
Leaf array with dates
Properties # Bundle manager Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique. title string mandatory The title of the element.</description></item><item><title>Nest</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/nest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/nest/</guid><description>Nest # The nest field is a container field. It can define multiple input fields, which are displayed as a subform. You have to focus the nest-field the show the sub form. The output is a dictionary with values from the sub form fields.
nest unfocussed
nest focussed
Properties # Bundle manager Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique.</description></item><item><title>Pull</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/pull/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/pull/</guid><description>Section # The pull field is a container field. It can define multiple input fields. The fields defined in a pull are displayed at the same level as other fields next to the pull field. The values are stored as dictionary below the pull key.
Example use of the pull field. The fields author and Description are show at the same level as the Title field
Properties # Bundle manager Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique.</description></item><item><title>Section</title><link>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.quiqr.org/docs/02-reference/03-content-model/03-form-fields/container-field-types/section/</guid><description>Section # The section field is a container field. It can define multiple input fields, which are displayed as a sub form. The output is a dictionary with values from the sub form fields.
section
Properties # Bundle manager Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique.</description></item></channel></rss>